>> Kyle Simpson: 让我们确保在整个未定义的问题上完全清楚
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's make sure we're
fully clear on this whole undefined
与未申报的事物之间的关系。
versus undeclared thing.
也许能对你们一些人进行审查但我们要确保我们的安全
Might be review for some of you but
let's just make sure we're fully clear.
未定义和未声明的差别是什么 ?
What is the difference between
undefined and undeclared?
有人吗
Anyone?
>> 扬声器 2: 您正在声明此变量存在，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: You're declaring
this variable exist,
我不是给它赋值而是存在的
I'm not assigning it a value but it exist.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好的，那是真的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay, that's true.
>> 扬声器 2: 因此已声明但未定义。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So
there it's declared but not defined.
>> 凯尔辛普森: 好的。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Okay.
>> 扬声器 3: 未声明。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Undeclared.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 好吧，那是其中的一部分，你是在正确的轨道上，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, that's part
of it, you're on the right track but
这还不是全部的
that's not all of it yet.
>> 扬声器 3: 未声明的内存从未在
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Undeclared has have
never had the memory allocated during
编译器解析阶段，而未定义。
the compiler parsing
stage whereas undefined.
也许它被分配了但从未被赋予过这样的价值
Maybe it was allocated but there's
never been a value assigned to that.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森:
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Putting both of
你的答案我们可以得到完整的答案
your answers together we can
get the complete answer.
因此，让我重申这一点。
So let me restate that.
你俩都是对的
You are both correct.
你是在正确的轨道上让我重申这一点
You're on the right track so
let me restate this.
这两者之间的差异，未定义的表示变量存在，但
The difference between these two,
undefined means a variable exists but
在它没有价值的时候
at the moment it has no value.
它可能从来没有价值，或者曾经有价值，也没有价值
It may have never had a value or it might
have used to have a value and it doesn't
但是空间的真空中没有其他的值是没有定义的，是吧 ?
anymore but there is no other value in the
vacuum of space it is undefined, right?
即使发音与未声明的同义词相似，仍未声明
Undeclared even though they sound
like synonyms undeclared is actually
从未正式宣布过任何我们可以进入的范围
never formally declared in any
scope that we have accessed to.
这就是未申报的意思
That's what undeclared means.
我们没有大理石。
We do not have a marble for it.
在严格的模式下，它总是会产生这些参考区域，好吗 ?
And in strict mode, it always results
in those reference areas, okay?
保持直线是很重要的
It's important to keep those straight.
不幸的是， JavaScript 试图解决这一问题并假装
Unfortunately, JavaScript tries to
mess around with this and pretend that
未声明的类型与未定义的相同，并且有一些错误消息
undeclared is sort of the same thing as
undefined and some of its error messages
还有其他的东西和东西在历史上是个很糟糕的想法
and other outputtings and things and
not is historically a really bad idea.
我们需要把这两个概念分开。
We need to keep these
two concepts separate.
有不同的东西被宣告不存在
There's a different something
being undeclared doesn't exist,
并明确定义它确实存在但没有价值
and being undefine definitely it does
exist, but doesn't have a value.